A Guide to the Papers of John McLaren McBryde, 1900-1907
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Beinkampen-Blount, 1900-1904. (Box-folder 1:30)
  - b: Advertisement for Photo-negative album and everyday file.
  - c: Advertisement for fine toilet papers with price list for J.P. Bell Co., 1901.
  - d: Notable letterhead from The Bain Peanut Co., 1901.
  - e: Correspondence from Norfolk and Western Railway Co. from a potential student, Frank Bell.
  - f: Notable letter from Confederate soldier, H.R. Berkeley, wanting to send his boy to V.P.I. for electrical engineering, 1902.
- Blackford-Bormay, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 1:31)
  - a: Notable letterhead from J.C. Blair Co., 1902.
  - b: Notable letter and letterhead from the manager for Frieda Siemens a well renowned German Pianist, 1903.
  - c: Pamphlet advertisement of Uncle Sam's Favorite, (Mailboxes).
  - d: Notable letterhead from Baugh and Sons Co., 1903.
- Boss-Brooks, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 1:32)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Royalton Woolen Co., 1903.
  - b: Letter from the Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, requesting the University to see if there were any summer positions for open for work during the summer, mainly in Mattress making and mattress repairing, 1902.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Norfolk and Western Railway Co., 1903.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Braddock and Co. on the back of the letterhead is the explanation of the Braddock System and how it works. " The best, safest, least expensive and most accurate system for conducting a Credit or Company Store Business."
- Broaddings-Byers, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 1:33)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Blue Ridge Springs Va.
  - b: Notable letterhead from J. Thompson Brown & Co.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Maryland Trust Co., 1902.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Buena Vista Plaster and Mining Co., 1901.
  - e: Notable letterhead from J. Bumgardner Distilling Co., 1902.
  - f: Notable letterhead from The Orton, 1901.
- Untitled folder- -Contains Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box-folder 1:34)
  - a: Notable letterhead for the Orange Judd Co., 1904.
  - b: Letter from A.S. Capehart, 1901 regarding sending a copy of the Paris Exposition of 1900 to V.P.I. (Explains what the exhibition was and the what the report includes.)
  - c: Letter in Spanish from El Presidente de la Audencia de la Habana, Fardieras, 1900.
  - d: Series of 28 letters in Spanish to McBryde and Tagliafero from Buenos Aires, Castro family. Additional letters in English from Peter Castro to his brother, sent from V.P.I. and from Julio de Cardenas to McBryde.
- Catlett-Coates. (Box-folder 1:35)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Riter-Conley Manufacturing Co., 1902.
  - b: Notable letterheads from Central Manufacturing Co., 1901-1902.
  - c: Notable letterhead from A.J. Chewning Co.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Chicago House Wrecking Co., 1902.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Thomas L. Cleaton, 1904.
  - f: Notable letterhead for Columbia Typewriter Manufacturing Co.
  - g: Agreement to furnish coal to V.P.I. Institution from July 1903-July 1904, Contract made in writing between Plunket and V.P.I. July 1903.
  - h: Notable letterhead for Pocahontas Coke and Coal Co.
- Coken-Courtuery, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 1:36)
  - a: Notable J.H. Collinson XC'LENT, Baltimore Oysters, 1902.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Columbia Shade Cloth Co., 1904.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Corbin Cabinet Lock Co., 1902.
  - d: Cortwright Metal Roofing Co. order form, 1900.
- Untitled--Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box-folder 2:37)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Hotel Stratford, 1902.
  - b: Notable letterhead from The Craig Art Co., 1903.
- Original Documents from folder 37. (Box-folder 2:38)
- Dabney-Deuman. (Box-folder 2:39)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Geo. D. Witt Shoe Company, 1900.
  - b: Letter from a parent with child being harassed at V.P.I.
- Originals from Folder 39: Dabney-Deuman. (Box-folder 2:40)
- Deuman-Dyer, 1900. (Box-folder 2:41)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Pentagraph Printing and Stationery Co., 1900.
  - b: Dow Wire Works Co., advertisement for tinned wire carriers for wheels, 1900.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Drewery, Hughes Co. Importers of dry goods, 1900.
- Originals from folder 41: Deuman-Dyer, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:42)
- Eakle-Eley, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:43)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Royalton Woolen Company.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Murphy's Hotel, 1903.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Elmer & Amend Importers & Manufacturers of chemicals, 1902.
  - d: Notable letterhead from The Letterman Company Department Store, 1901.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Electrical World & Engineering, 1901.
- Untitled--Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box-folder 2:44)
  - a: Sample of engraving for College Publications.
  - b: Notable letterhead from August Gast Bank Notes & Lithographing Co.
  - c: Series of letters from various engraving companies for diplomas etc.. with price ranges and other company information included.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Electric City Engraving Co., 1900.
- Fairback-Fills, 1902-1903. (Box-folder 2:45)
  - a: Notable letterhead from D.M. Osborne & Co., 1903.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Crucible Steel Co. of America, 1903.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Griffith & Griffith original Stereoscopic Views, 1902.
- Fitts-Fussell. (Box-folder 2:46)
  - a: Notable letterhead from the State of New York Department of Agriculture, 1903.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Fox Typewriter Co. Ltd., 1902.
  - c: Notable letterhead from "The Commercial", 1904.
  - d: 5 Southern Express Co. Tickets with rates on back, from Boston to Christiansburg for Cargo.
  - e: Postcard Advertising "The Columbian Cyclopedia Annual for 1900."
- Gaddy-Gill. (Box-folder 2:47)
  - a: Notable letterhead from New York Steam Packing Co.
  - b: Notable letterhead from The Orton.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Trenton Rubber Mfg. Co.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Aldophus Blair and Sons, 1903.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Camp Manufacturing Co., 1902.
  - f: Notable letterhead from William C. Geraty Co.
  - g: Letter from Office of the Chief of Ordinance, United States Army, 1902, Order forms for artillery and uniform pieces.
  - h: Notable letterhead from Murphy's Hotel, 1903.
- Gilbert-Graves. (Box-folder 2:48)
  - a: Memorandum of credit from the office of Ginn & Co. Publishers, 1901.
  - b: Receipts from Ginn & Co. Publishers.
  - c: Notable letterhead from F.L.G.H. & Company, real estate, rental and Insurance, 1901.
  - d: Standard letter for class failure from Registrars Office, 1904.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Aetna Insurance Co. of Hartford.
  - f: Notable letterhead from the Florida Hospital for the Insane.
  - g: Notable letterhead from the Grand Rapids Clocks and Mantel Co., English Hall Clocks, a specialty, 1900.
  - h: Notable letterhead from School Furniture Works, 1900.
- Gray-Gualthaney. (Box-folder 2:49)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Wm. N. Grubb Insurance, 1903.
  - b: Letter referencing a strike at the Virginia Passenger & Power Company from a father whose son failed out of Tech, 1903.
  - c: Advertisement for The Globe-Wernicke membership card index outfits.
- Hagood-Harrison, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:50)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Penn Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1900.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Lowell Model Co., Manufacturers of gasoline engines and attachments, 1903.
  - c: Letter from Don P. Hasley, State Senator from the 20th Senatorial District.
  - d: Notable letterhead from the Bain Peanut Co., 1904.
  - e: J.L. Hammett Company, 1901.
  - f: Notable letterhead from Hammond Typewriter.
  - g: Notable letterhead from Jefferson Hotel Company, 1901.
  - h: Notable letterhead from Harman Bros. Whiskey merchants, 1902.
  - i: Notable letterhead from Harris & Crismond Co.
- Harrison-Henderson. (Box-folder 2:51)
  - a: 7 letters from the Cuban Educational Association of the United States of America, 1900.
  - b: Letter from Frank Hart, a Confederate Soldier who lost his leg in the Civil War. He wants to give his son the education he never got, July 20, 1903.
  - c: Letter regarding additions to V.P.I. Faculty, salaries included, July 1901.
  - d: Notable letterhead from R.B. Chaffin & Co. Real Estate Agents, Brokers and Auctioneers.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Hansbrough & Carter Insurance, Real Estate and Loan, 1900.
  - f: Notable letterhead from Richmond Free Street Fair, 1900. List of people involved on the side.
  - g: Letter from G.W. Koiner, Commissioner of the U.S. Department of Agriculture, explaining the Farmers' Institutes.
  - h: "Institute Report for the Year ended, June 30, 1904, Queries" a form to fill out.
  - i: Letter with Article Attached titled "Cotton Rushed Up: Honors of the day were with the bears after hard struggle."
  - j: Notable letterhead from The Henderson-Ames Co., Military & Society Uniforms and Equipments, Regalia & Paraphernalia. Includes sample of white wool cloth, 1901.
  - k: Check written to Military and Society Uniforms and Equipment.
  - l: 5 Credit memorandums from Henderson-Ames Co., 1901.
- Henkel-Hodges. (Box-folder 2:52)
  - a: Notable letterhead from The Jno. J. Mitchell Co., 1903.
  - b: Notable letterhead from the Office of the American Publishers Association, 1904.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Julius Hines & Son, 1900, 1904.
  - d: Notable letterhead from L.R. Shepherd & Co., 1901.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Hirshberg Hollander & Co., 1901.
  - f: Notable letterhead from Tip Top Restaurant.
  - g: Notable letterhead from A. Hoen & Co. Lithographers, Engravers and Printers, 1903.
- Hoge-Howerton. (Box-folder 2:53)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Galeridge Institute, 1901.
  - b: Notable letterhead for Horlicks Food Company.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Wm. H. Horstman Co., 1904.
  - d: Two samples of white wool cloth, Columbia and Army Standard from Wm. H. Horstman Co., 1904.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Virginia Bridge and Iron Co., 1901.
  - f: Notable letterhead from H.B.Howes Crescent Falls herd of pure bred and grade Hereford cattle, 1902.
- Howison-Hylton. (Box-folder 2:54)
  - a: Notable letterhead from the Smith Premier Typewriter Co., 1903.
  - b: 5 Letters negotiating a trip to the Charleston Exhibition with the Stonewall Jackson Institute in Abington Virginia, all girls school.
  - c: Letter from the Mississippi Experiment station, 1903 regarding the most economical way of sending circulars with different machinery.
- Original Documents from folders 53 & 54. (Box-folder 2:55)
- Ide-Johnson, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:56)
  - a: List of old infirmary equipment.
  - b: Notable letterhead W.P. Ives & Co. Rectifiers and Blenders of old Whiskey, 1904.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Dental Snuf Company, 1900.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Bluefield Coal and Coke Co., 1903.
- Johnson-J. J. Julia Co., Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:57)
- Kable-Kyle, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:58)
  - a: Letter from a company with sample of calligraphy for diplomas, 1902.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Thomas Kane & Co. Works, 1902.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Fred Kauffmann, The American Tailor, 1901.
  - d: Letter from Agriculture College of Utah regarding State money and Legislative actions dealing with funding.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Providence Hospital.
  - f: Notable letterhead from Muphy's Hotel.
  - g: Notable letterhead from The Egg Reporter, a Journal For the Egg Trade.
  - h: Notable letterhead from King Mantel Company, 1900.
  - i: Advertisement for the N. Klein & Son Co., New England Pressing iron, Chinese Laundry Iron, Chinese Common Sad Iron.
  - j: Notable letterhead from N. Klein & Son, 1901 Sunshine Stores, Ranges & Furnaces.
  - k: Notable letterhead B. Kuppen Heimer & Co., 1902.
  - l: Notable letterhead from The "Oakley" Nelson Co. Virginia, 1901.
- Lachlan-Lilley, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:59)
  - a: Notable letterhead from S.A.L. Hotel & Dining Station.
  - b: Letter of recommendation for the nephew of General Beverly H. Robertson of the Confederate States Army, 1903.
  - c: Letter from Landes Photographers, 1901 concerning the request from the cadets for a reprint of a picture of McBryde.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Levey Bothers & Co. Inc., 1900.
  - e: Notable letterhead from The M.C. Lilley & Co., Military & Society Goods., 1903.
- Lilley-Lyon, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:60)
  - a: Receipt from The M.C. Lilley & Co.
  - b: Notable letterhead from The Rich Patch Iron Company, 1900.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Look & Lincoln Wagons, 1900.
  - d: Business card for Mr. Lovelock (Judging Cattle.)
  - e: Notable letterhead from The Lutz Company, 1902.
- Manufacturers Record Publishing Co.-Massenburg, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 2:61)
  - a: Receipts from the Fred Macey Company, 1900-1901.
  - b: Letter regarding problems with a fake receipt from Mallory.
  - c: Receipt from Norfolk and Western Railway Co.
  - d: Notable letterhead from J.H. Marsteller, 1901.
  - e: Pamphlet on illegal Practitioners and Consequences in Virginia.
  - f: Postal Telegraph-Cable sending an application for a free scholarship recommended by State Senator D. Gardiner Tyler.
- Massenburg-McColl. (Box-folder 2:62)
  - a: Letters from a worker for the Consular Service, USA in Buenos Aires, 1901.
  - b: Letter from Consulate D. Mayer about students from Buenos Aires and his son, 1900.
  - c: Map of the United States of the back of The National Irrigation Association, Letter addresses the National Irrigation Movement and a message from President Roosevelt to Congress.
  - d: Notable letterhead W.N. McAnge & Co., 1902.
  - e: Circular of V.P.I., a notice to professors concerning a class attendance.
  - f: Notice of vacancy form from the School and College Bureau.
  - g: Notable letterhead from Castner, Curran and Bullet Sole Agents for Pocahontas Coal, 1904.
  - h: Notable letterhead from John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1902.
  - i: Business Card for R.L. Meade, representing Charlottesville Woolen Mills.
- McCormie-Meade. (Box-folder 2:63)
  - a: Notable letterhead McGray refrigerator and cold storage Co., 1902.
  - b: Mailing card for "The Educational" periodical for the interchange of thought, includes Aim of the magazine and subscription price.
  - c: Telegram from Southern Railway Co., 1902.
  - d: Business card for R.L. Meade, representing Charlottesville Woolen Mills.
- Original documents from folders 62-63. (Box-folder 2:64)
- Meade-Mills. (Box-folder 2:65)
  - a: Dining hall evaluations by a designated board of students, (cadet captains.)
  - b: Notable letterhead from Chas. R. Linc Company, Druggist and Seedsmen, 1902.
  - c: Notable letterhead from University College of Medicine, Richmond, VA, 1901.
- Miller-Moore, 1901-1904. (Box-folder 3:66)
  - a: Letter from H.L. Newbold, Captain Artillery Corps to the Inspector General, U.S. Army. A submitted report of an inspection of the Government property at the Virginia Polytechnic Institute, May 21, 1902.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Monroe Refrigerator Company, 1900-1901.
  - c: Postal Card from the Montgomery Ward Company, 1904, receipt of order.
  - d: Postal Card with prices for various subscriptions from Moore's Subscription Agency, 1903.
- Moore-Myers. (Box-folder 3:67)
  - a: Letterhead from Headquarters of the Grand Camp Confederate Veterans, 1902.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Strother Drug Co., 1901.
  - c: Letter referring to the form letter from the registrar's office about class failures.
  - d: Letter including an article titled " The Academy and the Higher Institution, their relation."
  - e: Notable letterhead from Ed DeMoulin and Bros., 1902.
- Nash-Nutty. (Box-folder 3:68)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Neostyle Co., 1901.
  - b: Notable letterhead from "The Breakers," 1902.
  - c: Correspondence with a Students father over an alleged forged check, 1903.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Nonotuck Silk Company, includes price list, 1901.
  - e: Notable letterhead from The Nut Shell Publishing Company, 1901.
- Oakes-Owens. (Box-folder 3:69)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Stephen Putney Shoe Company, owners of Battle Axe.
  - b: Statement from Orange Judd Co., 1902.
  - c: Letter from the Office of the Chief of Ordnance U.S. Army, concerning the return of bond for corrections as pointed out by Judge Advocate General, USA-V.P.I.
  - d: Pamphlet form Ordnance Department U.S.A. titled " Regulations, Etc., For the Issue of Ordnance and Ordnance Stores to Colleges and Universities."
  - e: Invoice of Ordnance Stores amounting to 123.32$ to The Commandant of Cadets, V.P.I., July 1900 from the Springfield Armory.
- Patton-Payne. (Box-folder 3:70)
  - a: Notable letterhead from The National Hotel, 1900.
  - b: Notable letterhead from The Parker Pen Company, 1902.
  - c: Credit memorandum to Dr. Tagliaferro for 3.07$, 1901 from Parker Pen Co.
  - d: Request form submitted by Lewis Payne, Dec. 1902. Cadet Private in Band Company.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Adams Bros.-Paynes Co., 1903.
- Payne-Pollak. (Box-folder 3:71)
  - a: Receipt to Book and Uniforms department V.P.I. with note from V.T. Peed.
  - b: Notable letterhead from G. Penn Sons Tobacco Co. Manufacturers, 1903.
  - c: Notable letterhead from the Pettibone Brothers Manufacturing Company, 1901.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Judson L. Thomson Manufacturing Company, 1902.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Massie and Pierce Wholesale Lumber, 1903.
  - f: Notable letterhead from Ludwici Roofing Tile Co., 1902.
- Pollard-Quitman. (Box-folder 3:72)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Sunset excursions Washington-San Francisco line, 1903.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Cincinnati's Gibson House and Grand Hotel, 1903.
  - c: Legal document signed by McBryde for debt of 2$ from the Publishers' Collection Agency, includes statement of Law, 1901.
  - d: Notable letterhead from Queen and Co. Incorporated Manufacturers of Scientific Instruments, 1900.
- Original Documents from folder 72. (Box-folder 3:73)
- Rader-Regester. (Box-folder 3:74)
  - a: Notable letterhead from The New St Charles, 1901.
  - b: Notable Letterhead from Blue Ridge Springs, 1902.
  - c: Item and price list for Raub and Co. Publishers, 1901.
  - d: Letter from the Dean of the Administrative Board at Tufts College, Gardner C. Anthony, 1902.
  - e: Letter from English High School in Providence R.I. about gathering material for a museum used for teaching commercial Geography.
  - f: Advertisement for Reid Copy Holder, A.B. Reid & Co.
- Regester-Riggan. (Box-folder 3:75)
  - a: Notable letterhead from The reliable Incubator and Brooder Co.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Remington Typewriter, 1904.
  - c: Business card from Rida bock & Co. New York.
  - d: Prices for military & band equipment.
- Riggs-Roth. (Box-folder 3:76)
  - a: Notable letterhead from the Bedford Bulletin, Publishers and Job Printers with circulation for the year 1901-1902 on side of the stationary.
  - b: Letter from a parent regarding the typhoid scare, November 1903.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Buena Vista Plaster and Mining Co., 1901.
  - d: Advertisement & Letter for Wrights Concert Band.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Seaboard Air Line Railway, includes a map of the Southeast coast and the locations where the train stops.
- Rath-Ryland. (Box-folder 3:77)
  - a: Letter from the superintendent of Public schools of Warren Co., G.E. Roy, Front Royal, 1902.
  - b: Notable letterhead from The Royal Tailors, 1903, includes a list of uniforms they make, in the left margin of stationary.
  - c: Notable letterhead from The Great Southern Despatch, includes map on the back of the South East Fast freight line and connections.
  - d: Letter from H.H. Royer student seeking retribution for items that were stolen from him, 1900.
  - e: Letter from the department of education of Puerto Rico about sending boys to school at Blacksburg and the financial aide, free board, and tuition for these students, 1900.
  - f: Notable letterhead from The Virginia Cattle Food Co.
  - g: Purchase receipt from the Department of the Interior, 1903.
  - h: Notable letterhead from Wm. West Co., 1901.
- Sackett-Scott. (Box-folder 3:78)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Salem Heating Co., 1900.
  - b: Letter from the World's Work about V.P.I. as a leading technological school. request to include the school in the publication, 1900.
  - c: Notable letterhead from the Johnson Grocery Co., 1903.
- Scott-Sheldon. (Box-folder 3:79)
  - a: Notable letterhead from The Prudential Banking and Trust Co., 1902.
  - b: Notable letterhead from R.B. Chafin and Co., 1900.
  - c: Booklet titled "Some Aspects of the Analyzing and Grading of Iron Ores of the Gogebic Range." by Edward A. Separk, 1904.
- Sheldon-Smidon. (Box-folder 3:80)
  - a: Notable letterhead from Druggists and Seedsmen Co.
- Smith-Sydnor. (Box-folder 3:81)
  - a: Business card from architect Walter Jefferson Smith with a letter concerning the erection of a new building on campus.
  - b: Notable letterhead from The Smith Premier Typewriter Co., 1903.
  - c: Notable letterhead from The Hotel Chick Springs, 1902.
  - d: Notable letterhead from H.L. Smith, 1903.
  - e: Notable letterhead from B.D. Smith and Brothers, 1902.
  - f: Receipt from The Smith-Courtney Co., 1900.
  - g: Notable letterhead from Michigan Agricultural College, 1901.
- Soule-Stevens. (Box-folder 3:82)
  - a: Correspondence between Andrew Soule from the University of Tennessee and McBryde about moving to Blacksburg and taking a position, includes details about the house being built for Soule and his wife, 1904.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Southern Electrician, 1903.
  - c: Receipts of payment from the Southern Stamp and Stationery Co., 1902-1903.
  - d: Notable letterhead from The Southern Industrial News, 1902.
  - e: Sample of a blank form for keeping records in testing annual legumes, sent by the United States Department of Agriculture, 1903.
  - f: Notable letterhead from Standard Paper Manufacturing Co., 1903.
  - g: Notable letterhead from Standard Sanitary Manufacturing Co., 1903.
  - h: Blank Contracts for South Carolina reports.
  - i: Notable letterhead from Wallace Stebbins and Sons, 1902.
- Stewart-Steele. (Box-folder 3:83)
  - a: Telegram sent through Norfolk and Western Railway Company from a conductor in failing health requesting information on a course in telegraphy, 1903.
  - b: Notable letterhead from Tate Spring East Tennessee, the Carlsbad of America, letterhead includes rates of board.
  - c: Receipt from the Stone Printing and Manufacturing Co. for the printing of the "Bugle 1901."
  - d: Notable letterhead from the Stone Printing and Manufacturing Co.
- Original documents from 83: Stewart-Steele. (Box-folder 3:84)
- Storey-Sykes. (Box-folder 3:85)
  - a: Notable letterhead from The Western Assurance Co., 1901.
  - b: Advertisement from Isaac A. Sheppard & Co. with pictures and prices for a nine plate stove for wood, plain top tailor stove and a round top tailor stove.
  - c: Notable letterhead from Straus Gunst and Company, 1902.
  - d: Printed review of a book titled "A History of the German Language from the Present Day." by Chas. W. Super.
  - e: Notable letterhead from The Geiser Manufacturing Co., 1902.
- Tabb-The Times. (Box-folder 3:86)
  - a: Letter from the University of Florida concerning the question of Co-Education in higher institutions, seeking V.P.I.'s opinion, 1903.
  - b: Notable letterhead Treacy, Morris & Co. Manufacturers, 1903.
  - c: Series of letters in Spanish from Sates 1900's, from Cuba.
  - d: Notable letterhead from The Office of City Clerk, 1901.
  - e: Notable letterhead from Wm. H. Horstmann Co., 1903.
  - f: Notable letterhead from Hodnett-Chism-Thompson Co. Inc., 1903.
  - g: Notable letterhead from The Times, 1900.
- The Times-Urquhart. (Box-folder 3:87)